<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FLEX APP</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">By using the FLEX Android App, you agree to the following terms and conditions:

Data Handling:

FLEX collects and stores user data solely for the purpose of providing services and improving user experience.

User data is protected by secure encryption and stored on a secure server.

FLEX does not sell or share user data with any third parties.


Terms of Use:

The FLEX Android App is provided "as is" and is intended for use as an EMG therapy log to monitor patient\'s progress across their treatment of the Neurogenic disease.

Users of the FLEX Android App are solely responsible for the accuracy and completeness of the data they provide.

FLEX is not responsible for any consequences that may arise from the use of the app.


Privacy Policy:

FLEX respects user privacy and is committed to protecting user data.

FLEX collects user data solely for the purpose of providing services and improving user experience.

FLEX does not sell or share user data with any third parties.

FLEX may use user data for research purposes but will always anonymize the data before using it for research.

Users can request to access, modify or delete their data by contacting FLEX support.

By using the FLEX Android App, you agree to the above terms and conditions.
</string>

    //Headings
    <string name="step0Heading">What Will You Need</string>
    <string name="step1Heading">1. Be Comfortable</string>
    <string name="step2Heading">2. Clean the Skin</string>
    <string name="step3Heading">3. Electrodes Setup</string>
    <string name="step4Heading">4. Apply your Electrodes</string>
    <string name="step5Heading">5.Plug in the module</string>


    //Description

    //list slide
    <string name="step0_description">A place to sit or lay down \n Sanitizing Wipes \n Your FLEX Sensor!</string>

    //Step1 slide
    <string name="step1_description">Sit or lay down depending on \n which muscle you\'re performing \n the test</string>

    //Step2 slide
    <string name="step2_description">Using a sanitizing wipe, clean the skin where the electrodes will be placed</string>

    //Step3 slide
    <string name="step3_description">Place the surface pad into the attatchment that is connected to a cable</string>

    //Step4 slide
    <string name="step4_description">1. Apply the red lead on bony body part :wrists, knee, ankle, elbow \n 2. Apply the green and yellow leads next to each other on the muscle of testing</string>

    //Step5 slide
    <string name="step5_description">"Make sure to plug in the gray cable to the module to make sure your readings are taken correctly </string>

</resources>